nice to meet you.
初めまして
I heard about it, but is it a girl?
話聞いたんですけど、 少女なんですか?
Yes, it was my first time just now.
はい、さっきちょっと、初めて
Please take a moment to look at the camera over there.
ちょっと、そこのカメラを見ながらお願いします
Yes, I understand.
はい、分かりました
I think it would make me nervous.
緊張すると思うんで
Yes, I'm nervous.
はい、緊張します
So what about second sex?
じゃあ2回目のセックス?
Yes, that's right.
はい、そうです
How old are you?
いくつなんですか?
Now I'm 16 years old.
今、私は16歳です
16 years old?
16歳?
I'm still a high school student.
まだ高校生です
Isn't it a crime?
犯罪じゃないですか?
Makes you feel good.
気持ちよくします
Yes, I understand.
はい、分かりました
Can I have a strange experience with you?
僕の不思議な体験していいですか?
yes.
はい
May I?
いい ですか?
Next, let's have this one.
じゃあ次はこっちの一杯
yes.
はい
both.
両方
Please take down your pants.
で、パンツ降ろしてください
It's a little embarrassing though.
ちょっと恥ずかしいけど
Look at it a little earlier.
もうちょっと前に見て
yes.
はい
Try reaching out a little.
ちょっと手伸ばしてみて
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Once on the other side.
反対側も一回
Do more of what you said earlier.
さっきのもっとやって
It's like breasts.
おっぱいなみたいな
This hand.
こっちの手を
yes.
はい
I'm only 16 years old.
まだ16歳だもんね
Give me a little lick at the end.
最後ちょっと舐めて
Shall we do it?
していこうか
It's so gentle and feels good.
その優しくて気持ちいい
I'm glad you came.
来ててよかった
Let's lick various things inside and down, slowly licking various things.
いろいろ中とか舐めつつ下に、ゆっくりいろいろ舐めながらいこう
mosquito.
か
16 years old The various attacks are amazing.
16歳 いろいろ攻撃すごいね
Let's experience various places.
いろんなところ体験しよう
Shall we try it out?
体験してみようか
Are you going to do that?
そんなにしていきます?
Do you want to do that so much?
そんなにしたい?
You want to, right?
したいでしょ?
16 years old.
16歳
Do you want to do that so much?
そんなにしたい?
I'm also embarrassed by my appearance.
僕の格好も恥ずかしい
Is this enough?
ここまででいいんですか?
Please give me a blowjob.
フェラーをしてください
Just with your mouth, without using your hands.
手を使わずに、口だけで
While looking at me.
僕のことを見つめながら
wonderful.
すばらしい
Are you being stared at?
見 つめられてる?
difficult.
難しい
Then please go to sleep.
じゃあ寝てください
It's only my second time.
まだ2回目だから
Ah, I see, it's only the second time.
あ、そっか、まだ2回目か
I want to cry a little.
ちょっと泣きたい
It's very beautiful nearby.
すごい綺麗な近くにしてる
Are you going to sleep?
寝ます?
Wait for the footsteps.
足音待って
Just do your best for now.
今だけ、頑張って
It feels amazing.
すごい気持ちいい